A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
DO NOT ENTER
WARNING! DANGER
How are you?
How's life?
Are you happy?
With yourself? With everything?
How many years has it been?
So much has happened.
Births, weddings, funerals...
without each other.
But we were the start of it all.
Just being ourselves.
Do you still cross the line?
Are you still the rule-breaker?
Or are you just another brick in the wall?
It still feels unreal,
the things we went through.
What were we?
Us. Our gang. "The worst."
That's what they called us.
"The worst."
♪ Pull oar gently
Gently ♪
♪ The Dervish with patience ♪
♪ Attained his desire ♪
♪ He said, "Slow down" ♪
♪ To those who are in a hurry ♪
♪ He said, "Beware" ♪
♪ Gently ♪
Hey. Anything I should know about?
- What's up?
- It's bad.
- What?
- Shithead's onto us.
Osman... The infamous Osman...
So you put together an army of nerds.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Trading homework, you little shit!
Hey, hey listen, okay?
It's not a big deal.
It's really good for the entire school.
This way, everyone's a winner.
Fuck off!
Come on, let's go!
Get open!
Yeah, baby!
- How was that not a foul?
- It's nothing.
- Can't you see? He pushed me!
- Play on.
I will fuck you up!
Get off of me! Don't touch me! Get off!
I'm gonna fuck you up!
Are you a moron?
Is this the first time
you've ever been fouled?
I don't give a shit if you're
the star player! You're off the team.
Get out of my face!
You're so hot.
Someone's gonna hear us.
No, they won't. Everybody's outside.
You sure?
Mr. Tarik!
Necdet, we were just...
- Just what? What, Mr. Tarik? What?
- Please, sir. I can explain...
I'm not interested in
your explanations.
Pack your things,
and get the hell out of my school!
Disgusting.
God, look at that creep.
Poor guy.
What's that?
He wrote me a farewell letter
before he left.
On pink paper.
Anyway, what are we doing after school?
In philosophy,
an ideal intellectual entity...
I was hoping you wouldn't show up.
Like you had died or something.
Not yet, unfortunately.
Close the door, please.
We haven't covered much, but I'll give you
the notes on what you missed.
Sinan, I watched this movie last night.
It was so romantic.
I think you'd like this one.
Please don't.
No, hey. Kevin Costner is in it.
I've always thought
he's such a sweetheart.
He plays a retired athlete.
It's not like the ones you normally
get to see, but, you know,
the houses and everything in the movie
were just so beautiful.
All right, guys, listen up. I can see
how very excited we all are today.
We all support our debate team,
and we wish them the best of success.
You will be missing
your first two periods.
And instead, you will get to watch
the debate competition in the auditorium.
How fun.
Of course, they've decided to bring
their own students,
so I expect you all to behave.
It's our responsibility to host them
in the best possible way that we can.
Whether we win or lose, we are going
to do so with grace and honor.
- It's great to see you both, gentlemen.
- A pleasure.
- I feel a victory coming.
- Oh, yeah? You sure about that?
Hello, everyone!
Welcome to our distinguished school.
I want to tell you
about a little game I like to play.
A game in which everybody wins.
I'm giving one to two odds on a tie.
We win, it's a triple.
You win, it's a 3.5.
I'm taking all payments up front.
- Where the hell is Sinan?
- We don't know where he could be.
Why did we let him join the team
in the first place?
He might know a lot, but it won't matter
if he doesn't show up.
He'll be here.
- Yavuz, go and find out where he is.
- Yes, ma'am.
Pain in the ass!
- Hey, man. Where does this go?
- Huh?
I don't know.
Can you move? I'm busy!
- Just tell me where to put this.
- Put it wherever you like. I don't care.
Fine. I'll just leave it here, bitch.
- What's going on?
- Help!
Are you okay?
Please, if everyone can take
their seats, the debate is about to begin.
13TH HIGH SCHOOL DEBATE COMPETITION
Debate's starting. Bets are closed.
Unfortunately, our sound system
is down,
which means we have to continue without
the use of any microphones.
And for that, I apologize.
Please enjoy the debate.
Hurry up, ladies.
Eda, what are you doing out here?
Go in the auditorium.
Yeah, I'll get there.
Go!
Eda?
What's up?
Uh, not much.
Why don't you go get us some coffee?
- But-but...
- I'll watch over the booth.
Don't worry.
Go fetch us some coffee,
and then we can chat a little bit.
Well, okay, then. I'll get us some coffee.
Be right back.
Yeah, yeah, no rush.
Don't worry about it.
All right...
First of all, I would like
to welcome you once again.
Our topic is "individual vs. society."
Let's start with team blue.
İSTANBUL ULUCINAR HIGH SCHOOL
The individual is more important.
Although we can't deny the basic fact
that in our society,
it is absolutely necessary
to raise children. We...
Don't stop.
Uh, right. Where was I?
Uh, first of all,
we can't deny the basic fact
that in our society,
it is absolutely necessary...
What's going on?
Society is...
- Hey, they're trying to rig this shit!
- Hang on. It's just an accident.
This isn't fair! It's not an accident.
You have to call off the bets.
They didn't even get a chance to talk.
They're distracted.
Kids, it's important
that we stay calm,
and let's stay in our seats.
Eda. Of course it's you.
Are you trying to drive me
completely insane?
I am so fed up with you!
It's no big deal. Don't be mad.
It was just a joke.
Enough! Find yourself a seat
in the auditorium, and be quiet.
I'm going to deal with you
when this is over.
Can you just go one day
without causing any trouble?
- It's all yours.
- Eda?
Uh...
Don't ever leave your post again!
You understand? Move!
The general welfare of society
plays a critical role
in elevating the individual.
From this perspective, we can comfortably
say that society is more important.
The individual is simply one part
of a greater whole.
Thus, with the absence of society as a
whole, the individual loses its function.
To provide an example, uh...
let's talk about an individual
who voluntarily isolates himself.
For you see, this individual, after
removing all connections from society...
When it's your turn,
the lights are just fine.
Shut up! We didn't do this shit!
Dude, you're being crazy.
I never play dirty.
Bullshit!
What's going on?
What are they fighting about?
We had a bet,
but they keep playing dirty.
Right, they're up to something.
How do you know?
I heard. They're trying to play you.
Bro! They totally rigged it!
Shh! Settle down!
Let's think about an individual
who voluntarily isolates himself.
All right.
This individual,
after disconnecting from society,
begins to lose social skills
that he has acquired.
This gives us a very clear picture
of society's importance.
It is society that makes an individual
an individual
- and gives a person a sense of meaning.
- Who threw that?
The fuck's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, what's that?
Who the hell do you think you are, man?
Talking back to me?
You're on my fucking turf!
♪ I started walking ♪
Break them up! Hey!
♪ Then I realized
I am in the beginning again ♪
Stop this now! Behave!
♪ In the beginning ♪
♪ I started thinking ♪
♪ Then I realized
I am in the beginning again ♪
♪ In the beginning ♪
♪ I started walking ♪
♪ Then I realized
I am in the beginning again ♪
♪ In the beginning ♪
♪ I started thinking ♪
♪ Then I realized
I am in the beginning again ♪
♪ In the beginning ♪
♪ And suddenly everything ♪
♪ Everything is good ♪
♪ Everything seems great to me ♪
Stop it! Kids, oh, my God! Fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
♪ Everything is good ♪
♪ Everything seems great to me ♪
♪ I started rioting ♪
♪ Then I realized
I am in the beginning again ♪
- Why is this happening to me?
- ♪ In the beginning ♪
♪ I started rioting ♪
Hell, yeah!
♪ Then I realized
I am in the beginning again ♪
♪ In the beginning ♪
Necdet, this is unacceptable.
You are absolutely right, sir.
Let me promisethat...
I haven't seen
anything like this in my entire career.
That was an absolute frenzy.
I'm disqualifying your school.
You're banned from this debate
and all future debate tournaments.
- You're out. Got it?
- Yes, of course, sir. As you wish.
- You and your school are done for good.
- Well, have a good day, sir.
What's taking them so long?
Just call us in and get it over with.
This is bullshit.
Are you looking at me?
No, I wasn't. I was just thinking.
Did you break the amp?
Yeah... What about you?
Nothing. Just routine stuff.
I was going to win big
if you hadn't messed with the lights.
Uh, do you think I care?
What did he do?
Set the curtain on fire.
Our student representative is here.
- Işık, how are you, my dear?
- I'm doing very well, thank you, sir.
Sorry, sorry, traffic was a nightmare.
Well, since Ms. Distas
has decided to show up,
I think it's time we get started.
Have them come in one at a time.
I thought the light show
spiced things up a bit.
I think everybody had fun.
Get out.
All right, Kerem...
You were the one who broke the amp.
Or rather, you broke it by smashing it
on your classmate's head.
Well, it was completely random.
It could've happened to anyone.
The amp?
Well, that thing was pretty old.
We needed a new one anyway.
You'll need a new spine
after I'm done with you.
You nitwit!
Can you believe this?
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
amidst the chaos, I was able to keep
some of the down payments.
How about I buy the school a new amp,
and we forget this ever happened.
Hm?
There you go.
This is what we're dealing with.
We need to act!
I refuse to defend myself.
'Cause defending oneself is an
admission of guilt up to a certain point.
It's basically saying
I could have done it, but I didn't.
What are you rambling about?
You almost burned down the school!
Are you familiar with Schrödinger's cat?
There's no such thing as "almost."
Until the moment
the school is burned down,
it is both burned and not burned.
And in this case, since the building
clearly hasn't been burned down,
- do you understand what I mean...
- That's enough! This is absurd!
He's testing our patience.
This has gone too far.
Get out.
Now!
I hate these kids.
Someone always wants to be merciful
so we can't expel them.
Unfortunately, a majority vote
is not enough.
It has to be unanimous.
I believe we'll have unanimous consent
this time.
Twelve out of 12, right?
Well, aren't we?
We had nothing to do
with each other back then.
We weren't even friends.
It feels so weird to even think about.
What do you mean you're not on board?
We got kicked out of the tournament.
What else do you want?
Yes, but shouldn't we look at this matter
from the perspective of the students?
Look, we're talking about
denying them a formal education...
Yeah, so what?
How can you say that? They'll never
even get a high school diploma.
I do not care at all! This is their fault.
It's not like they're going to contribute
to society, are they?
They'll all be in jail before they even
turn 20. They're evil brats.
I agree. Especially Eda.
I'm sorry, but her mother gave birth
to a witch.
Also Sinan and Kerem.
Those two are insane.
I'd agree with that.
Kerem is the worst of all.
That kid scares me.
He's seriously dangerous.
You're making this situation
very personal, and you shouldn't.
It's too late!
Those four kids come in every day
and make our lives a living hell!
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
I feel like our decision
is not based on this one incident,
but on everything they've ever done to us.
Why should I care?
Those kids are a plague on this school.
We've gotta get rid of them for good.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
We're not being objective.
This is not the constitutional court.
And I agree with Mr. Refik.
Personally, I think we should stop
dragging this matter
and move straight to voting.
Ms. Distas, please don't make this harder
than it has to be.
Come on. Let's vote.
That's it. Hold 'em up.
Burcu, you're feeling guilty
for no reason. There's no need to.
Mm-hmm.
Let's get 'em this time. Keep 'em up.
Come on.
- Are we really getting expelled?
- Of course not.
I'm here every month. They need to
vote unanimously, but they never do.
She's right. Last month, I got through
with two votes.
Two votes? That's really close.
My best score is four against eight.
So, four people felt so sorry,
they let me stay.
But this time...
It'll be fine.
What did we even do?
Goddammit.
Here, hazelnuts.
I'll take some.
Thanks.
You bastards
will get what's coming to you.
But not today.
Eleven to one.
You got away again,
you pathetic delinquents.
I couldn't expel you this time.
But I will.
In fact, if I had one more day left alive,
I'd spend it
trying to get you all expelled.
You hopeless sociopaths!
Another narrow escape.
Eleven to one.
I wonder who saved us.
Look who it is,
our student representative.
She's the head of the honorary committee.
She sits in
on all of the disciplinary boards.
What? What are you doing? What's going on?
Sinan! Sinan.
Who was the one that voted for us?
What?
Someone saved us.
We want to know who it was.
That's secret. I can't tell you that.
Come on, don't be like this. Just tell us.
- Eda, really, I'm not allowed...
- Tell us!
Distas. It was Ms. Distas.
They tried to expel you all, but she
refused to consent and stood up for you.
So she's the reason
we didn't get expelled.
- It's just...
- What?
Stop yelling.
She's getting flustered.
Ms. Distas is really committed.
She didn't want anyone getting expelled.
Those were the times
when standing out meant being punished.
If you're different, too bad.
Just be normal, ordinary.
Burcu wasn't aware of anything.
It was only her conscience.
Her trying to be fair.
Having a sense of justice
was more important to her
than just about anything.
♪ Where do I come from?
Where am I going? ♪
♪ Where am I?
I want to know ♪
♪ I am looking for love
I worship the beauty ♪
♪ Am I a human?
I want to know ♪
♪ I suffer pain
I am shedding tears ♪
♪ Am I in love?
I want to know ♪
Grandpa, wake up.
Dinner's ready.
♪ I am going to mountains ♪
♪ I am running in the rain ♪
♪ Am I insane?
I want to know ♪
Dad?
Oh, Sinan. Nihal likes this,
so I'm taking it to the house.
Tea?
I don't have time. Gotta get dinner ready
for the twins.
Can't talk right now.
Come in.
BURCU DISTAS
IS HEREBY TO BE TRANSFERRED
TO THE EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTION
DESIGNATED...
Oh, yeah.
Hey. Anything I should know about?
What is it?
What?
Sinan! Sinan!
Come here! Hurry up!
Shit.
What's up?
Ms. Distas is being reassigned.
She's leaving in two months.
They'll definitely expel our asses now.
Finally.
I wanted this appointment so badly.
Congratulations. I think this will be
a great step in your teaching career.
Thank you.
Sir, you're going to leave those kids
alone when I'm gone, aren't you?
Of course not! I'm kicking them out.
You are?
Yeah. A red card!
Sir, I'm begging you.
Oh, I've waited long enough.
I'm doing it.
Well, then... I'll postpone my relocation
for a whole year.
Come on, now.
You know, you...
You're being ridiculous.
Okay, I won't.
Promise me?
Yes.
Maybe if we can just behave
and not end up in front of
the board again...
Yeah, right.
Every single teacher hates my guts.
They'd expel me
if I looked at someone the wrong way.
- Especially after what I did.
- You mean banging the teacher?
Watch what you say,
or I'll break your goddamn jaw.
Oh, yeah?
Guys, can we just focus for a second?
This is serious.
Shithead got the news.
I can't waste more time with you.
I'm gonna talk with Ms. Distas.
We're neighbors.
She borrows sugar from my mom.
Don't worry, Eda. He promised me
he won't go after you when I leave.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Turns out Ms. Distas is an idiot.
She says Mr. Karakis
promised not to go after us.
- Promised? Karakis?
- He'll expel us for sure.
- Hey, you gonna talk to Ms. Distas?
- Yeah, like I report to you.
Uh-oh.
What now? You just gonna keep
sending your little nerds?
We need to do something.
Who's "we"?
Everyone should save their own ass.
No. In dire times, people in the same
situations need to unite.
So let's do it.
All we have is each other.
Eda, those girls you hang out with
would leave you in a heartbeat.
Kerem, we saw how much
your team stood up for you.
Such insightful observations.
What about me? I don't give a fuck
about getting expelled.
If you're expelled now, the name Karakis
will haunt you for the rest of your life.
Will you be happy knowing
that this asshole Karakis
was the person that
determined your future?
This shithead?
Make that 12 lahmacuns,
and I want six of them spicy.
- Come on in.
- Ayran, too. Of course.
I gave you the address, right? Okay, bye.
So convenient.
You have quite the appetite.
- It's gonna be crowded.
- What do you mean "crowded"?
Let's just get this over with, shall we?
Let's wait for everyone.
Move, Sinan.
Make sure to use a lot of lemon.
Pass the salt.
- Come on!
- One sec.
Mm, this lahmacun is so nice and crispy.
I know. Roll it up like this.
- Hey, are you having any?
- I don't think so. Ugh.
Do you really live here all by yourself?
My mom and dad both have other families.
So they left me our old house.
They're seriously fine with you
living all alone,
in this house with no adult supervision?
There is an adult. My grandpa.
- I'll take this one.
- Go for it.
Oh, wow.
There's actually someone over there.
- Are you sure he's alive?
- He's always like that.
We really cut it close this time, guys.
We would've been fucked
if it weren't for Ms. Distas.
I don't normally like teachers,
but she's actually pretty nice.
I guess she's nice. Tough, too.
But she's naive.
She desperately wants to be
a good person,
and she has too much faith in people.
Hey, let's just focus on solutions.
Now, let's find a way out of this.
Let's beat up Karakis.
But like really rough him up.
Like break his arm.
Or put him on payroll. Make him one of us.
Oh, wow. Such brilliant ideas.
How do you balance with those
giant brains in your head?
Just forget about Karakis. What we need
to do now is focus on Ms. Distas.
Get her transfer revoked.
That's our only way out.
Hmm.
If she gets married, she can stay
in whatever city she wants.
So she has to marry someone in Istanbul.
So one of us proposes to her?
Oh, yeah, she'd totally marry you.
I'm sure her dream is to marry
some lame-ass high school student.
Wanna get hit?
Sure. Why not?
Ms. Distas is a romantic.
She needs to fall in love first.
Oh, wait, wait, that's it!
We'll make her fall in love.
How do we do that?
Love is overrated.
You guys can chat about it,
but leave me out of it.
All I know about love...
if someone loves a person
who doesn't love them back,
then they're just trapped, you know?
It's confusing and unnecessary.
They'll love you if you give them
what they want.
If they don't, they'll leave you.
And you feel like total shit.
That's the point.
Love is about self-interest.
If you give them what they want,
they stay,
but the moment you stop, they leave.
It's a stupid game, that's all.
Bravo! You're all such experts
on the matter.
Love is fucking stupid. It's not for us.
I agree. It's dumb.
Well, since none of us believe in love,
we're going to find someone who does.
But we'll need help.
We'll make her fall in love,
she'll get married, and settle down here.
And the four of us get to graduate.
Okay, deal.
But who are we going to get
to help us out?
We don't know shit about love.
You know very well who we're going to get.
Oh, God! You can't be serious!
LOVE IN CHAINS - DOMINIC BENDEL
Hey, get out.
We need to talk.
What about?
What are you guys doing?
- Sit down.
- Don't touch me! Oh, my God, can you...
- Relax. Sit down.
- Let go!
Sinan, can you say something to them?
Leave me out of it.
- What is wrong with you?
- Sit still for a sec.
- You're scaring her.
- It's okay. We won't hurt you.
Işık, listen...
Listen, honey...
Ms. Distas is going away.
No, she can't leave.
I love her so much.
Then you should help us.
Romance is what you know best.
We have to make her fall in love.
Otherwise, she'll leave.
Ms. Distas is going away.
I have so many fond memories.
You know I'm going to miss her, too.
We're talking about making
something beautiful happen.
This is good for all of us.
Don't worry, they won't bite.
Though I'm not so sure
about this one.
Hey, cool it.
Please.
Come on. Will you do it?
Okay, I'll help you guys out.
Yeah! Told you.
Besides, it really is what I know best.
And plus, we get to spread love, right?
Yeah, you're so right.
First, we need to find a candidate.
That guy always has wet hands
for whatever reason.
Is he always in the bathroom,
or is it something else?
- How about him?
- Maybe he's the man of Burcu's dreams.
That guy's a dick.
Total asshole. It won't work.
No way!
ISTANBUL TEPEBAŞI HIGH SCHOOL
Is there anyone else it could be?
We're out of options. It's useless.
Found him.
♪ Darling, you got to let me know ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go? ♪
♪ If you say that you are mine ♪
♪ I'll be here till the end of time ♪
♪ So you got to let me know ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go? ♪
It's like he's made of fairy dust.
Fairy dust?
He used to play basketball
but became a coach after he got injured.
He's new.
He's so handsome.
Yeah, but we don't know what's he like.
He must be amazing.
That's definitely him.
- We found him?
- We have.
This is gonna be so exciting.
All right, then.
Let the operation begin.
♪ Should I stay or should I go? ♪
What a bizarre start we had.
The story that made us who we are.
I'm writing you this letter
because we're now at the end of the road.
Our history is disappearing.
Let's meet again.
Come, if you still care.
So that we can prove that we are real.
Or don't show up. And we will disappear.
Just like this place.
It's your call.
I'm sending this invitation.
I think it's worth it.
Don't you?
This ruin, our memories...
Don't you think they're worth saving?
Did we really exist?
Were we real?
I'm sending this to your most recent
address I have
since I don't know your current one.
I'll be waiting.
Please come, before it's all gone.